Hello, welcome to the Create Access website.
Create Access is about bridging the opportunity gaps in tech by offering accessible pathways
to 3D creation. And this website is
built to be able to expand upon the website that Create Access
already uses. To be to best succeed,
successfully help their students,
their partners, and anybody coming across their website.
To be able to best use their tutorials,
contact them, donate to them,
support the company in any way.
To be able to expand the 3D learning space.
firstly, we go over the home screen that we created,
or the home page that we created.
we started off by making sure that it got straight to the point,
being able to explain what this website is for,
and then being able to show the resources for that.
off some of the modeling for 3D creation,
what are some of the things that they can create. down below,
exploring what the journey of Create Access can show
you, what you can,
build upon, and some of the collaborators and businesses that partner with.
create access to be able to enhance these tutorials and the learning for students.
On here, our plan would be to expand upon it to a full page.
As more partners come in, as descriptions or their roles change,
that would be the page that people- to see those changes and
be able to be caught up.
firstly, on the Nav Bar, we kept it simple,
with the main things that you needed as any type of user on
the website to be best- succeed on it.
which would be the courses,
the About Us text, I have to learn more about the company,
a way to contact directly and donate section,
and then the download would be directly for the software being used,
which would be downloaded directly from Epic Store.
Firstly, let's start off with the courses. So for the courses,
the one problem that we- so with the main website was just unclear of
where to start.
so right away, what we wanted to begin with was showing the microcourses
hub, showing exactly what the software you're using is,
and a way to just begin right away.
So when you go off of the courses,
you have the option right here to just read on what the software you're
using, which is Unreal, and the Unreal Engine Editor,
which is a free software that Epic does provide,
for people to work on, create games,
expand upon a four-night, three-model,
etc.
and we do add some guides at the bottom that show a lot of
the different movements,
the controls that you would need to understand what to do in these softwares,
which is very helpful and accessible to all people using those tutorials.
right away, we wanted to make, sure that we had a section that could
go right into the different tutorials that you can go through.
So we have, as soon as you hit,
start learning, we can pick through the different courses that we have.
Right now, for sake of implementation,
we added just two.
so when you go into here, it brings you through the courses,
where you'd be able to begin in order of which one you want to
go to, and you'll see the videos directly from the YouTube uploaded
videos that are provided from Create Access.
And through that, you'd be able to see,
all the guides, everything that you need,
and even link you directly to the PDF files for
the projects themselves so that you can visually see the steps as you're going
through the video.
As we do that,
it creates a way more cleaner and simple way for students to be able
to follow along, which helps in the long run of people staying on the
website, finishing their tutorials,
finishing, learning how to do 3D creation,
and in the end, makes creative- access more successful in the long run.
After this, we have the about section,
where we directly will go through the mission for create
access, what brings them, what drives them, the future plans so that it's
very clear to people that want to partner,
people that want to join, what the- what the movement of the company is,
where they're leaning towards, where they're hoping to achieve to,
and making that a hundred percent clear, especially,
since the whole point is for people to be able to join without restrictions,
it's a lot easier if people can see that fully laid out.
another way to just link them to connecting directly with Create Access
through e-mail, and be able to record that directly off the website,
and being able to see the full team of people that are amazingly
being able to increase and create an environment in this company
that lets- people learn amazing skills that they
wouldn't have been able to anywhere else.
so whether that's founders, the educators,
or some of the interns involved,
they'll be able to learn what their names are, who's gonna be actually helping
them and see that team. From there we also have just the contact
page. Again, this is where they'll be able to put their emails,
send a message to them so that they can get back to them and
best communicate with the team directly, I created access.
there's also a donation page which allows people that want to support and may
not be able to physically, you know, join the program,
but be able to continuously.
Give their support to a company that's trying to give free programming to students.
And then finally, the download page will bring you directly to the Epic Store
where they'll be able to find and download the support
for the Epic.
Unreal Engine Epic Engine.
that is our implementation for Create Access.
Although there's obviously a lot of things that we want to continue to add
to it. This is the structure and we feel like it simplifies it in
the best way that we can to be able to successfully support the students
and being able to quickly get to their courses, but also people that want
to learn and see all the in-depth information for it.
Thank you. Have a good day.